It seems we've reached the national border.
どうやら国境に着いたみたいだな
But with fog this thick, there's no
telling where the enemy is.
しかし こう霧が濃くちゃ
どこに敵がいるのかも分かりゃしないぜ
They're close, very close.
いますよ
すぐ近くです
The fog is lifting.
霧… 晴れる
About 10,000 or so?
１万… ってとこか
No, more like 50,000.
いや…
５万だ
This is a relief.
フッ 安心しました
It appears we've met our objective to draw
out the majority of the enemy's forces.
敵の主力を引き付けるという目的は
果たしたようです
I see.
なるほど
Well, I guess I'll be going on
a total rampage then!
じゃ！ 心置きなく
暴れまわってやりますかーっ！
おうっ！
kodomo no goro no yume wa
The dream I had when I was a child,
子供の頃の夢は 色褪せない落書きで
iroase nai rakugaki de
were drawn to my heart's desire
omou mama kaki suberasete
with scribbles that wouldn't fade away
思うまま書き滑らせて
描く未来へとつながる
egaku mirai he to tsunagaru
and are connected to the future i draw.
Utawarerumono
sumiwataru sora
The clear skies
澄み渡る空 果てしないほど青く
hateshinai hodo aoku
were endlessly blue.
mujaki na kokoro ni
And my innocent heart,
無邪気な心に 充たされ魅かれてく
mitasare hikareteku
being satisfied, was attracted to them.
yagate jiyuu ni tobimawareru
I finally obtained wings
やがて自由に飛びまわれる
翼(はね)を手に入れて
hane wo teni irete
with which I could fly freely.
muku na hitomi wa motometeku
I want to go to the end of the skies
無垢な瞳は求めてく
空の向こうへ 行きたいな
sora no mukou he ikitai na
which my pure eyes desire.
kore tonai negai kara
If one wish could be granted
止め処ない願いから 一つだけ叶うのなら
hitotsu dake kanau no nara
out of countless others...
dare ni mo yuzuri taku wa nai
I feel that it should be to grab onto a dream
誰にも譲りたくはない
夢を掴みたいと思うよ
yume wo tsukamitai to omou yo
and never be tempted to let go.
kodomo no goro no yume wa
The dreams I had when I was a child,
子供の頃の夢は 色褪せない落書きで
iroase nai rakugaki de
were drawn eternally,
itsuwademo kaki tsuzukerareta
with scribbles that wouldn't fade away
いつまでも描き続けられた
願う未来へとつながる
negau mirai he to tsunagaru
and are connected to the future I wish for.
End of the Banquet
Archers, take aim!
ペリエライ 構えっ！
うおおおーああーっ！
Fire!
掃射！
怯むなーっ！
Do not shrink from the enemy!
Crush them all!
押し潰せーっ！
Spearmen, forward!
We must not lose this ground!
クリリャライ 前へ
絶対 岸に上げてはなりません！
おぶっ
ぬうあっ！
-くりやあーっ！
-はっ
ぜえっ
どわっ
グワアーッ！
ふんっ
All right! Let's charge forward!
よっしゃあーっ！
このまま一気に！
We must not.
Huh?
いけません
なあ？
General, why not?
大将
何故？
我々の役目は
ここに敵を引き付けて時間を稼ぐ事です
Our duty is to draw the enemy
forces in and buy some time.
But General...
しかし…
If we were to charge at them,
we would not last for even a moment.
こちらから攻め入れば
半刻と持たないでしょう
I guess we have to trust the
Commander to do the rest.
後は総大将を信じるのみですかい
I'm counting on you, Highness.
頼みます 聖上
クエーッカッカッカッカッカッ
臭う
I smell it! I smell the stench of the beast!
臭うぞ 獣の臭いがな
滅びを運ぶ獣が
すぐそこに近付いておるわ
The beast that brings about destruction
is very close by.
のわっ くっ…
あっ のわっ かっ…
-えっ！
-どわあっ！
-ふんっ！
-うああっ あ…
あ あ あふああ…
ご苦労だった トウカ
Well done, Touka.
次は私の番ですわね
My turn next, right?
ふああっ！
ヘッハハハハハハハハハハハハハ
Good! Good job!
良い 良いぞ
Lord Hakuoro!
ハクオロ殿
Looks like we're finally in for some fun.
これでやっと退屈せずに済みそうだわ
Hakuoro, we'll take your head!
ハクオロ王！
そなたの首 貰い受ける！
Prepare yourself!
覚悟ーっ！
ええーっ！ えあーっ！
Eruruu, stay by me.
エルルゥ 離れるな
Right!
はい
でやあーっ！
ふええーっ！
Let the banquet begin!
宴の始まりよおっ！
とぅあーっ
-ふっ やっ
-どぅあーっ
たあっ！
があっ
いやっ！
エムロ！
Emuro!
私の一撃を受けきるとは驚きですわ
I'm quite surprised that you were
able to take a blow from me.
You monster!
この化け物め！
Oh, my, how rude!
あら 失礼ですわね
Don't get cocky.
いい気になるなよ
Our true worth is revealed when the
three of us combine our attacks.
俺たちの真価は
３人揃った時にこそ発揮されるのだ
てえっ！
Karula!
カルラ！
Lady Karula!
カルラ殿
Leave this to me. Please go on ahead.
ここは私に任せて どうぞお先に
I'm sorry.
すまん
くっ 逃がすかあ！
Don't let them get away! Inaushi! Ikoru!
イナウシ！ ニコル！
We'll make short work of this one
and go after Hakuoro!
さっさと そ奴をやり ハクオロを追うぞ！
Right!
おう！
Do you think it will be that easy?
そう簡単に行きますかしら？
てっ きいーやあーっ！
ううーおらあーっ！
てやっ！
とうっ
いひっ
うえい
てあーあーっ！
てりやっ
よいはっ
とあっ
えいっ
てやっ
いやあっ てぃやあっ
でぃえいっ！
You did well to avoid our attacks.
よくぞかわした
But you cannot win against us
simply by running away!
だが逃げてばかりでは我らには勝てぬぞ！
しあっ
ふあっ
I appreciate the warning.
ご忠告 感謝しますわ
Insolent little thing...
減らず口を
Die!
死ねええーっ！
てえーえーっ！
な なぜ？
H.. How!?
I was only heeding your warning.
忠告を聞いたまでですわ
I cannot win simply by running away.
逃げていては勝てない
But if I focus only on one, it doesn't
matter if there are three of you.
１人だけを見ていれば
３人いようと関係ありませんわ
くうっ
You monster!
この化け物めっ
あはっ あ…
So, which of you will be next?
さあ 次はどちらかしら？
-はっ！
-ごあっ
Those stairs will take us to
the king's chambers.
階段を上れば 王の間です
うああーあー
うああーあー　あああーあーあー
はあっ 何？
What?
この者達は…
What are these?
いったい…
カーッカッカッカッカッカッカッカッカ
How do you like my beasts?
どうだ 我が獣達は？ 気に入ったか？
Niwe!
ニウェ！
They are the most skilled warriors collected
そ奴らは
ワシが攻め滅ぼした国々から集めた
from the various countries that
I have vanquished.
選りすぐりの者達よ
They're excited because they want your blood!
貴様らの血を欲して 興奮しておるわ
What did you do to these men?
この者達に何をした？
I only awoke the blood of the beast
which was within them.
その身に眠る獣の血を
呼び覚ましてやったまでの事
もっとも…
ワシを満足させるには至らなかったがな
Still, there were none who could truly satisfy me.
The blood of the beast?
獣の血！
だが本当の獣を目覚めさせるためには
少しは役立つだろう
However, they may yet be of some use
in awakening the real beast!
クアーッカッカッハッハッハッ
Now, my precious dogs,
さあ！ 可愛い犬達よ！
feast upon their flesh and blood!
そ奴らの血肉を 存分に食らうがいい！
Protect Lord Hakuoro!
ハクオロ殿をお守りしろ！
うっうわっ！
ああーっあ！
ふんっ！
We slash them and slash them,
but they still keep coming!
斬っても斬っても きりがありませぬ
カルラさん
Karula-san!
If slashing doesn't do the trick,
then just dismantle them!
斬ってダメなら…
解体すれば済む事ですわ
Lord Hakuoro, leave this to us.
You take down Niwe!
ハクオロ殿 ここは任せてニウェを！
Eruruu, you stay here with Touka.
エルルゥ
トウカ達と ここに残れ
I'll go with you.
私も行きます
Eruruu!
エルルゥ！
I want to see this through.
私は見届けたいんです
I want to see the path you take
with my own eyes!
この目で ハクオロさんの行く道筋を！
Niwe, prepare yourself!
ニウェ！
覚悟！
クアーッカッカッカッカッカッカッカッ
So you've come,
来たか　我が愛しき獣よ
my delightful beast.
The battle is over.
もはや勝負はついた
If you quietly surrender, I will not take your life.
おとなしく降伏すれば 命は取らぬ
クアーッカッカッカッ 降伏だと？
Surrender, you say?
-クアーッカッカッカッカッカッカッカ
-何を笑う？
What are you laughing about?
War is like hunting.
戦とは狩りよ
You meticulously set out a trap,
then wait for your prey.
周到に罠を仕掛け 獲物を待ち続ける
After that, it's eat or be eaten,
one of the two.
その果てにあるのは食うか食われるか
二つに一つ
You've got to be kidding.
戯言をっ
Haven't had enough?
まだ足りぬか
Then I'll show you some more entertainment.
ならば 余興を見せてやろう
Wh... What was that sound?
何の音だ？
クーッカッカッカッカッ 教えてやろう
I'll tell you.
It's the sound of this country of
Shikeripechim being consumed in flames.
このシケリペチムが炎に包まれる音よ
This is absurd!
バカなっ…
Are you insane?
正気かっ！
What? It's no big deal.
なあに  大した事ではないわ
Shouldn't you be worrying more
about yourself instead?
それよりも自分の事を心配した方が
いいのではないのかな？
あああーっ やああーっ わああーっ
おおおーっ おうおう
ああっ ひどい…
How terrible!
Eruruu!
エルルゥ
Can you hear them? The voices of those
running and being burned?
聞こえるか？
炎に焼かれ逃げ惑う者どもの声が
Niwe, you...
ニウェ お前は！
They all think you're the one who did this.
皆 貴様がやったと思っておるぞ？
You are Hakuoro, the vile man who
burns the innocent to death!
無辜の民を焼き殺す極悪非道の男ハクオロ
クアーッカッカッカッカッカッカッカッ
Damn you! I will not forgive you!
貴様っ
許さん！
I like the tone of your voice!
It drips with rage and hatred.
いい声だ 怒りと憎しみに満ちておるわ
I've been waiting for this moment!
この時を待っておったぞ！
Niwe!
ニウェーッ！
ぬおーっ
Hakuoro-san!
ハクオロさん
Good! Very Good!
良い 良いぞお！
-クアーッカッカッカッ！
-えいっ！
ていっ
It is just as I had suspected.
さすがはワシが見込んだだけの事はある
I have fostered several over time,
これまでいろいろと育ててはきたが…
but you are the best!
やはり貴様が一番じゃあ！
What?
何？
ぬうーっ
ふんっ！
You still don't get it?
分からぬかっ！
Orikakan, this burning city,
all those men who died at war...
あのオリカカンも この燃える街も！
死んだ者達も！
They were all sacrificed in order to
raise the beast that is in you.
全ては汝という獣を育てるための贄よ！
How much must you make the people
suffer before you are satisfied?
どこまで人々を苦しめれば気が済むのだ！
You've got it wrong.
What!?
違うな
何？
The village of Yamayura, Orikakan,
the people of Tuskuru,
ヤマユラの里 オリカカン
トゥスクルの民も シケリペチムの民も
and even the people of Shikeripechim,
誰も彼も 貴様のために死ぬのだ
each and every one of them will die for you.
You are a beast that brings about disaster.
汝は災いを運ぶ獣じゃ！
If you intend to curse anyone,
you should curse yourself!
呪うなら その身を呪うがいい！
違う！
You are wrong! You are the culprit
behind this disaster!
貴様こそが災いをもたらす元凶だっ
I will take your head and cut off
this misery at its root!
その首を取り 一切の禍根を断つ！
たあーっ！
ふえあーっ！
いやあっ！
るうーあーっ！
Hakuoro-san!
ハクオロさん！
Is this the extent of your strength?
貴様の力は こんなものかあっ！
うえあーっ！
はああ… な 何？
Wh... What is that?
これよ…
This is it...
This is what I've been waiting for.
これを待っておったのよ
Lord Hakuoro!
ハクオロ殿！
Stay back!
来るなっ！
I will defeat Niwe.
ニウェは… 私が倒す
クアーッカッカッカッカッカッ
まさに獣の目！
Truly, the eyes of a beast! Come, Hakuoro.
来い ハクオロ
Let's go enjoy this where we
won't be interrupted!
邪魔の入らぬ所で存分に楽しもうぞ
Don't!
ダメェーッ！
Karula-san?
カルラさん
Lord Hakuoro!
ハクオロ殿！
Take care of Eruruu!
エルルゥを頼む！
うううっふっ
いやあっ！
たあっ！
-クアーッカッカッカッ
-いやあっ！
It dances! My sword dances!
-躍る！
-ううっ
-胸が躍る！
-ううあっ！
You are my ultimate prey!
-貴様は最高の獲物よ！
-うっ！ いえーっ！
What is this, this heightened sense?
何だ？ この高揚は…
Flames burn my throat and roast my flesh,
炎が喉を焼き 肉をあぶる
yet I can feel it throb.
なのに疼く！ 体が疼く！
My body throbs...
My blazing blood boils!
燃える血が煮えたぎる！
ふんっ！
クーックックックックッ
Feels good doesn't it, Hakuoro?
心地良い痛みよのお ハクオロ
Are you satisfied?
満足か？
Is this the conclusion you desired?
これが貴様の望んでいた結末か？
How many thousands of lives
こんな事のために…
何千何万の命をっ
have you toyed with for this!?
弄んだというのかあっ！
NIWE!
ニウェーッ！
Y... You're...
お お前はあっ！
クアーカッカッカッカッカッカッカッ
My sight was true after all.
やはり… この目に狂いは… 無かった
You... You are the ultimate beast!
貴様…
貴様こそが 最高の獣よ！
Now, go on and eat me.
さあ食らうがいい
In this existence, it's eat or be eaten.
我らに存在するは 食うか食われるかよ
クアーッカッカッカッカッ
カッカッカッカッカッカッカッ
What in the world did this?
これはいったい…
何が？
It seems His Highness has succeeded.
聖上がやってくれたようですね
炎さえも凍てついた
honou sae mo itetsuita
I seek the solitude
kokuno naka moto mu
that freezes even flames.
孤独の中求む
魂から結びつき 私を恋い温めて
tamashi kara musubitsuki
Connecting with your soul,
watashi wo koi atatamete
warm me with your love.
嗚呼 祈りの言葉がふるえ
a inori no kotoba ga furue
Ah...the words of prayer tremble...
嗚呼 弱きいのちが消えても
a yowaki no chika kiete mo
Ah even if the faint-hearted
were to disappear...
くりかえす 輪廻の流れ辿り
kurikaesu innen no nagare tadori
Following the recurring paths of fate.
終わらない世界の宿命を見つめてる
owaranai sekai no shukumei wo mitsumeteru
I gaze upon the never-ending world's destiny.
くりかえし 詠われる者達よ
kurikaeshi utawareru mono tachi yo
Oh the ones being sung continuously
守られてまどろむ宵
mamorarete madoromu you ni
be protected and sleep.
At the End of the Battle